[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1978 William Friedkin directed The Brinks Job. The movie was based on the 1950 armed robbery of the Brinks Building in which almost $3 million was stolen. Where did the robbery take place?", "correct_answer": "Boston, MA", "incorrect_answers": ["New York City, NY", "Pittsburgh, PA", "Baltimore, MD"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these commercial organisations was founded in 1947?", "correct_answer": "Indian Railways", "incorrect_answers": ["Microsoft", "Intel", "China Petroleum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This NFL team, established in 1933, plays its home games in Heinz Field. In 2008, ESPN.com ranked this teams fans as the best in the NFL partly due to their sellout streak of 299 consecutive games.", "correct_answer": "Pittsburgh Steelers", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicago Bears", "Dallas Cowboys", "New York Giants"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the street in New York City, famous for jewels and jewelry?", "correct_answer": "47th street", "incorrect_answers": ["Madison Avenue", "51st street", "Park Avenue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was special about the playing cards that were given to British pilots in World War II?", "correct_answer": "They turned into maps.", "incorrect_answers": ["They secretly listed safe houses to hide in.", "They contained the code words to alert British RAF headquarters about anti-aircraft emplacements.", "They had very sharp edges so they could be used as weapons."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the Cold War, which city was the capital of West Germany?", "correct_answer": "Bonn", "incorrect_answers": ["Munich", "West Berlin", "Frankfurt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Spanish playwright and poet, author of The Dog in the Manger and The Widow from Valencia,  maintained that a writers business is to write so as to make himself understood.", "correct_answer": "Lope de Vega", "incorrect_answers": ["Oscar Nareda", "Jose Ortega y Gassett", "Humberto Robinson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the sci-fi thriller Aliens, Cpl. Hicks believed the mission was going to be a stand up fight.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the only state whose legal system is not based upon English Common Law?", "correct_answer": "Louisiana", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "Alaska", "Texas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which baseball pitcher pitched 11 perfect innings, only to lose the game in the 12th?", "correct_answer": "Harvey Haddix", "incorrect_answers": ["Warren Sphan", "Lew Burdette", "Johnnie Sain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries is NOT fictional?", "correct_answer": "Central African Republic", "incorrect_answers": ["Central America", "Central Korea", "Central Europe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river named after a mythological figure is the longest river of Great Britain?", "correct_answer": "Severn", "incorrect_answers": ["Trent", "Great Ouse", "Thames"]}]